But I had some victories, so this
martini glass, there's
a thing in the book called the martini
principle, which is the idea that kind
of, if ever you never want to be alone
and just start to mix a martini
because
somebody will jump out from behind a
tree and say that's not how you mix a
martini.
And so the way that you know, the way
to find out whether you're doing
something
wrong or not is to start doing it
because somebody will jump out.
But what I wanted is, there's a
chapter in the book called chapter
ship.
And I wanted this chapter, I wanted a
skull and crossbones
on here, because it's a pirate ship.
In the book it's a pirate ship.
And so I sent them an icon that had a
skull and crossbones, but they just
put
the skull on. I've got no idea why.
And so I can't figure out whether
that's more badass or just annoying.
But the point I'm making is that kind
of, you get to a point where you
lose control.